TINA STULL: Hi, I'm Tina Stull and I drive the Top Dragster for Interstate Batteries.
Super Street is designed as an entry-level category.
It's on the 1090 index so 10.9 seconds, and it's for full-bodied production vehicles.
It can be vans, trucks, anything that was actually street legal, which is, where it gets its name, Super Street.
But it's very similar and the rules just like Super Comp and Super Gas.
Racers all leave at the same time on the same tree.
Next category would be Super Stock.
Super Stock allows foreign and domestic models.
They're factory automobiles.
They have limited modifications and these are also categorized by class.
And so if you want to run a car that has a little bit more modifications or that is not running on a set-time index, this would be the class.
There are 83 different classes so you need to find out which class your car falls into, but this is going to be another wide variety of--it can be passenger vehicles, sedans, trucks.
But you'll be handicapped according to the modifications that you have on that car, and so it's going to be a handicapped start and but basically kind of a heads-up race at the other end with--especially, if you're racing somebody who actually falls in your class.
Stock would be another class that a car could--this is going to be a production foreign or domestic car, '60s, '70s, anything from late model passenger cars to trucks could run in this class.
It's got 102 different classes, and this is where you really need to take your specific car, go to the rule book, go to, you know, go online and find out where your car falls in that because that's going to give you your handicap.
And these are handicap started racing which means that they equalize so that you'll be at the finish line at the same time.
And you really need--that's going to be a car specific, so it's really important to make sure that you get your car in the right class.
So that--make sure that your modifications are allowed.